Guide to the W. W. Morgan Papers circa 1905-1990
University of Chicago Library
- Series V: Administration and Organizations
  This series documents Morgan's service as director of the Yerkes Observatory, editor of the Astrophysical Journal, faculty of the University of Chicago, and mayor of the town of William's Bay, Wisconsin.
  - Abt Helmut, Classifications, Plate Shipments, 1968-1982 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Adler Planetarium, 1974-1979 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Midwest Center, 1975-1982 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Midwest Center, 1979 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Newsletters, 1979-1982 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Newsletters, 1979-1982 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - American Academy of Achievement Program, 1983 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - American Astronomical Society, June 3-7, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Anna Mininni, undated (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Atlas Publication, 1978 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: A, 1948-1952 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: B, Folder 1, 1948-1952 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: B, Folder 2, 1948-1952 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: C, 1948-1952 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: D-E, 1948-1952 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: F-G, 1948-1952 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: H-I, 1948-1952 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: J, 1948-1952 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: K, 1948-1952 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: L, 1948-1952 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: M, 1948-1952 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: N-O-P, 1948-1952 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: Q-R, 1948-1952 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Correspondence: S, 1948-1952 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Committee on Publications, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Committee on Publications Report, 1949-1950 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Committee on Publications, 1950 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Committee on Publications, 1951-1952 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Council Meeting, 1949-1952 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Hemens Correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Astrophysical Journal, IAU, 1948-1952 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Astrophysical Journal, Letters, Brogue Draft, 1952-1953 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Referee's Report, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Astronomical Society of the Pacific, 1975-1982 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Boller and Chives Spectra Comparator, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Book Orders, 1972-1982 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Burton F. Jones, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - B-Spectrograph, Checklist, 1958 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - B-Spectrograph, Instructions, 1962 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Cerro Tololo, Interamerican Observatory Proposals, Folder I, 1977 -1980 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Cerro Tololo, Interamerican Observatory Proposals, Folder II, 1977-1980 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Denver Trip, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Glass Copy of Palomar Altas, 1961 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Hobbs L.M., 1976-1985 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Hobbs L.M., CV and Papers, 1974-1987 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - International Astronomical Union, 1948 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - International Astronomical Union, 1952-1953 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - International Astronomical Union, 1985-1986 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Kron Richard Gordon, CV, 1984 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Langoford Historical Re-Prints, 1982-1983 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Memo, Meeting August 7th, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Morgan, Abt, Tapscott, Publications, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Lestina Letitia, 1979-1982 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Midwest Astronomer Group, 1975-1982 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Mihalas Dimitri, Theoretical Study, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1983-1986 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1986-1987 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Huntington Controversy, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Minutes and Reports, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Proposal Sheets, undated (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Report of the President, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - NASA, Annoucement of Opportunity, Hubble Space Telescope, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - NASA, Moon, 1966-1976 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - NASA, 1974-1982 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - National Research Laboratory, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - National Science Foundation, 1978-1982 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - National Science Foundation, Proposal Evaluation Forms, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Observer Infor, Kitt Peak Observatory, undated (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Observing Request, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Organizational Correspondence, 1985 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Planetarium Director's Lectures: "Some Discovery Made at Yerkes Observatory", 1984 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Plates Returned to Helmut A. Abt, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - Prints of NGC 628, undated (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Referee's Report, 1974-1978 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - Reidel D. Publishing Company, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - Report Commission 37, IAU, Clusters and Associations, undated (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - Report Commission 33, IAU, undated (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - Research Corporations, 1974-1979 (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - Royal Astronomical Society, 1977-1981 (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - Royal Danish Academy of Sciences, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 29)
  - Rudnick, Correspondence, 1941 (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - Staff Photograph, May, 1960 (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - Stromgren Bengt Visit, 1979 (Box 97, Folder 32)
  - University of Chicago, Annual Reports, 1964-1982 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago, Annual Reports, 1981-1984 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago, Annual Report, July, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago, Bulletins, 1975-1980 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - University of Chicago, Business, 1953 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago, W.W. Morgan Committee Reports, 1967-1969 (Box 98, Folder 6-9)
  - University of Chicago, W.W. Morgan Committee Reports, 1967-1969 (Box 99, Folder 1-6)
  - University of Chicago, W.W. Morgan Committee Reports, 1963-1967 (Box 100, Folder 1-4)
  - University of Chicago, Council Notes, 1952-1953 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago, Council, Senate, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago, Dean, 1981-1983 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago, Departamental Communications, 1952-1953 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - University of Chicago, Eckhart Library, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - University of Chicago, Garden Club of America, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - University of Chicago, Grounds Committee, 1981-1986 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago, Interdepartmental Communications, 1974-1978 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago, University News and Information, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - University of Chicago, retirement papers, 1956-1977 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Vatican, 1985-1990 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Vatican, 1985-1990 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - William's Bay, Village Business, Folder I, 1946-1948 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - William's Bay, Village Business, Folder II, 1946-1948 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - William's Bay, Village Business, Folder I, 1948-1951 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - William's Bay, Village Business, Folder II, 1948-1951 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - William's Bay, Water Safety, Committee, 1952 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - William's Bay, Water Safety, Committee, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Wirth Allan, Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Yerkes Observatory, Interdepartmental Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Series VI: Teaching
  - Albert E., Assistantship, January-March, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Classification Class, 1968 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Galaxy Class, 1969 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Galaxy Class, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Parker Committee, 1972 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Preliminary of Qualifying Exams, 1972 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Stellar Spectroscopy, List of Unknowns, 1963 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Stellar Spectroscopy, Exams of Unknowns, undated (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Walborn Nolan R., Thesis, Paper, Master Copy, February, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Walborn Nolan R., Thesis, Publication Version, 1970 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Walborn Nolan R., Thesis, Published Version, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Walborn Nolan R., Thesis, "Some Spectroscopic Characteristic of OB Stars", 1970 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - White Richard, Assorted Transparencies, undated (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - White Richard, Departure, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - White Richard, Thesis, 1973-1974 (Box 102, Folder 15)
- Series VII: General
  - "A Day in my Life", 1918 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - American Academy of Achievement, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - "Address to be Given at My Funeral by Dimitri Mihalas", 1986 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Addresses, undated (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Albert, Elise, Summer Project, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Alzheimer's Materials: Jean Morgan, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Amoco Orders, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Lease, 1970-1971 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Astronomy Biography, undated (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Adoubon Society, 1978-1979 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Automobile Accident, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Barnard E.E., Sketches Photocopies, undated (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Barrett Storrs B., Biography, 1938 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Bengt Stromgren, Death, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Billy Morgan, Boy Scout Membership Cards, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Biology, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Britannica Book of the Year, 1948-1952 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Catechism Certificates, 1913 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Chang Y.C., Death, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - Course Notes, Morgan, 1929 (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - Church Trustee, 1969-1973 (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - Church, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 1990-1992 (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - Draft Letter to R.E. Griffin, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 24)
  - Draper Medal 1979, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 25)
  - Draper Medal, Citation, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 26)
  - Executive Health, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - File, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - General Papers, 1922-1990 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - General Papers, 1986-1993 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Harper's Magazine, 1967 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Hidelbrand Roger H., 1987 (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Hobbs, Memo, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - House Lease, 1991-1992 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Income Tax, 1961 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Income Tax, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - IAU, 1980-1981 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - IAU, 1982-1983 (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - IAU, Commissions 45, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 13)
  - IAU, Commissions 45, 1977-1982 (Box 104, Folder 14)
  - Herschel Medal, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Journal Fragments, 1962 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Journal Pocket Notes, undated (Box 104, Folder 17)
  - KPNO Newsletter, 1980-1983 (Box 104, Folder 18)
  - Letter to Aizenman, 1980 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Letter to Bryce Crawford, with Enclosures, 1985 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Loebb Anthony J., Movie, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Looking Inwards, May 7, The Presence of God; May 14; The Pursuit of God, May 21, 1972 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Mail to Answer, 1985-1987 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Mail, 1983-1986 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Mastercard, Fenruary, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Maupassant, Contes de Guerres, with Vocabulary, 1916 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Memorial List for Helen B. Morgan, 1963 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Mihalas Dimitri, Journal Excerpts, 1983-1987 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Mihalas Dimitri, Poetry, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Mihalas Writings, undated (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous, 1974-1982 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975-1983 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, A-M, 1981-1982 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, M-Z, 1981-1982 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, N-Z, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - MKK Atlas Booklet, 1943 (Box 105, Folder 18)
  - The MK Process, 1985 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Morgan W.W., Funeral Program, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Morgan W.W., Obituaries, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Morgan W.W., Reemplyment, 1958 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Morgan W.W., Spectra TV, undated (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - The New Yorker, July 27th, 1963 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - North Coast Indian Calendar, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - NSF, National Medal of Science, 1976-1979 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Observatory Photos, undated (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Our Church Work, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Papers, 1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - PASP, Picture, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Photo Envelope, 1944 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Preface to the Complete poems of Carl Sandburg, undated (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Pontifical Academy, Photos, 1970 (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Pontifical Academy, Newspapers Clippings, 1964 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Quadrangle Club Membership, 1975-1978 (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Quadrangle Club, 1978-1980 (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Retirement Dinner, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 19)
  - Roach Franklin, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 20)
  - Stromgren Bengt, Death, 1987 (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Sky Maps, 1985-1986 (Box 106, Folder 22)
  - Tapscott J., Memorial, 1978 (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - Tapscott J., 1970-1980 (Box 106, Folder 24)
  - Telephone Conversations, 1974-1975 (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - Sandage Allan, Pontifical Academy, Medal of Gold Attribution, pope Pius XI, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - The Listening Service, Grant Proposal, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Townes Charles H., "Science and Religion", 1966 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Townes Charles H., "Science and Religion", 1966 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - To Mr. Morgan, 1960 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Trustee's Dinner, 1974 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Type A, undated (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - United Church of Christ, Membership List, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Universidad Mariana de Cordoba, Honorary Degree, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - University of Wisconsin - Madison, Commencement Program, 1992 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - University of Wisconsin - Madison, Honorary Degree Album, 1991-1992 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - van Biesbrock, Biography, undated (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Washington, Hotel Prices, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Walterman Alan T. Award, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Weaving, undated (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Wheeler J.A., "The Universe as a Home for Man", 1987 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Wheeler J.A., Arrow of Time, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - Wheeler J.A., Manuscript, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - Wisconsin Rotary Club, Certificate, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Yale University, Honorary Degree, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Yearbook of Walworth County, Wisconsin, 1947 (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Yerkes Observatory, Postcards, undated (Box 107, Folder 22)
  - 50th Anniversary Reception Guestbook, 1976 (Box 107, Folder 23)
  - 50th Anniversary, Adler Planetarium, Certificate, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 24)
  - Pontifical Academy, Pontifical Academician, Medallion, 1967 (Box 108)
- Series VIII: Photographs
  It is likely that most of these photos were taken by Morgan. The series also contains some files of older photographic portraits of other Yerkes astronomers, as well as other early Yerkes memorabilia. Most of the photography is artistic and was kept in no particular order. This series shows the amazing work of an unknown photographer.
  - Subseries 1: Photographs
    - Album 1, 1934-1953 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Album 2, 1940 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Astronomer's Portraits, 1915-1930 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Arrangements (Some May Day), 1981 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Barnard E.E., Photos, undated (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Carmella, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Crawford Photos, undated (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Emily and van Biesbrock Kids, n.d (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Fall, undated (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Flowers (Multiple), 1977-1980 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Flowers, 1977-1981 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Front Walk from Window, undated (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Frost Family, undated (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Group Photos, 1922 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Helen Barrett and W.W. Morgan, circa 1926 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Leaves, undated (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - McCuskey, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - McDonald Observatory, 50th Anniversary Photo, 1989 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Photos, undated (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Morgan W.W. Photography, 1933-1934 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Morgan W.W. Photography, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Morgan W.W. Photography, undated (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Morgan W.W. Photography, undated (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Morgan W.W. Photography, undated (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Morgan W.W. Photography, undated (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Morgan W.W., Portraits, 1935-1971 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Morgan W.W., Portraits, 1956 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Mostly Trees, undated (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Old Yerkes, undated (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Photo Mailer, undated (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Scrapbook, 1947-1951 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Scrapbook, undated (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Tapscott J., 1965 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Tracks, Ice, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - van Biesbrock, undated (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Wedge Scales, undated (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Yerkes Observatory, 1919-1949 (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 2: Negatives
    - At the U of C, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Collection Negatives, undated (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Nine Pictures in Ohio, 1914 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Negatives, undated (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Negatives 1, undated (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Negatives 2, undated (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Negatives 3, undated (Box 112, Folder 7)
- Series IX: Oversize
  - Blaau, Star Maps, undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Astronomer's Portraits, undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Telescope Scrapbook, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Morgan W.W., Portraits, undated (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Staff Picture, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Tables and Graphics, undated (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Pontifical Academy, Diploma, undated (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - W.W. Morgan Photography, undated (Box 114, Folder 3)
- Series X: Restricted
  - Agnes Drabek Social Security, 1969, R-50 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Agnes Drabek Social Security Correction, 1973, R-50 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Astronomy 411, Spectral Classification, Winter, 1968, R-80 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Carl Sagan, Grades and PhD. Examn, R-80 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Code's Master's Thesis, Grades, 1947 R-80 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1969-1990 R-80 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, W-X-Y-Z, 1948-1952 R-80 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Crewe A.V., Dean, 1974-1980 R-80 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - E.D.S (General Motors), July, 1985, R-50 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Elan Financial Services Correspondence, 1985, R-50 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Gallagher J.S., 1977-1983 R-50 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Income Tax, 1962, R-50 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Income Tax, 1963, R-50 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Income Tax Papers, 1965, R-50 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Lakeland Hospital, 1987 R-50 (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - NSF - AST-8007988, Budget, 1980-1983 R-50 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - NSF - AST 80-07988, Final Report, Nov. 1, 1980 - Apr. 30, 1983, R-50 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Papers, 1978-1989 R-50 (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - Qualifying Exams Answers, May, 1972 R-50 (Box 115, Folder 19)
  - Sapida A.C., M.D., 1989, R-50 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Scientific American, 1988, R-50 (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Taxes & Budgets, 1956-1963, R-50 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Tax Receipt Envelope Budget Book, 1956-1960, R-50 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - The Astrophysical Journal Report of Referee, 1974-1982, R-50 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - W.W. Morgan, Testament, 1986 R-50 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - White Richard, Letters of Recommendation, 1973-1980 R-80 (Box 116, Folder 7-8)